koreaherald.com 2005-10-12

# The Korea Herald : The Nation's No.1 English Newspaper

The Korea Herald maintains a rigorous standard to protect the personal information of members subscribing to our Internet services. In this regard, we are adopting a number of relevant guidelines in accordance with the 'Law Pertaining to the Promotion of Use of Information and Telecommunication Networks' and the "Guidelines for the Protection of Personal Information" enacted by the Ministry of Information and Communication. 

The Korea Herald home page clearly indicates how and for what purpose members' personal information is used. It also describes the steps implemented to ensure the protection of personal information in accordance with relevant laws and amended government guidelines. It also discusses any changes that may occur in the scope of its services.

For questions about changes in the status of our policy of personal information protection, please contact the staff members listed at the bottom or visit our home page.

**Purpose of Our Collection of Personal Information**  
Most of the services provided by our home page can be used at any time without user registration. However, there are occasions, as in the case of a special event or a contest, in which we may collect personal information through questionnaires for the purpose of improving our customer service.

**Provision of Information to a Third Party**  
The Korea Herald makes a point of confining the use of personal information about its members to the scope stated in the foregoing paragraph, and strictly prohibits our employees from further use of this information or its sharing with a third party. These restrictions may not apply in the event that a customer permits the release of his or her personal information, or if a government institution asks for its use under relevant laws.

**Inspection, Correction and Deletion of Personal Information**  
Any member of the Internet services provided by the Korea Herald can inspect or correct his or her personal information or ask for the deletion of his or her ID at any time by clicking "Correction of Member's Personal Information" or sending an explanatory e-mail to a staff member in charge. The requested change in information will take effect directly upon completion of the relevant procedure.

**Technical Measures Taken for the Protection of Personal Information**  
The Korea Herald applies the following technical measures to prevent loss, theft, disclosure or forgery of your personal information:

1) Your personal information is protected by means of a secret access code, and important data is protected by additional security measures.

2) User information is protected by means of a secret access code and can only be corrected or deleted by the user him or herself or a system operator authorized by the Korea Herald. Do not disclose your secret access code to a third party. Should you need to use a computer provided by a public institution or share a computer with others, please do not take choose to have your secret access code automatically stored on the hard disk. In addition, take other necessary steps for the protection of your personal information, such as making sure that your work has been closed properly.

3) The Korea Herald is using a device to block intrusion from outside, including hacking.

**Collection of Personal Information by Means of Cookies**  
The Korea Herald uses cookies to store and recall member information in an effort to provide more personalized and customized service. A cookie is a small data package sent by the website server to a user's browser. It is stored on the hard disk of a member's computer.

We can make our service more useful and easy to use by obtaining a clearer picture of how our members use, surf, and visit our online services, using cookies.

By choosing one of the options given in the web browser, you can accept all cookies, check whenever a cookie is stored, or refuse to have any cookies stored.

**Period of Retention and Use of Personal Information**  
As a member of the Internet service provided by the Korea Herald, your personal information will be retained by us and used only for the provision of member services. In the event that a member asks for the deletion of his/her ID or cancellation of subscription, in accordance with the procedures stated in the foregoing "Inspection, Correction and Deletion of Personal Information," or if the purpose of our request for use of a member's personal information has been attained as notified in advance, the relevant personal information collected will be irretrievably deleted from our hard disks.

**Commissioned Processing of Personal Information**  
The Korea Herald reserves the right to depend on an outside source for the commissioned processing of members' personal information in order to enhance the quality of our services.  
1) You will be notified of the fact should your personal information be processed on a commissioning basis.  
2) Please rest assured that when we depend on an outside source to process your personal information, all due care will be taken to instruct the service provider on the strict protection of personal information. This includes the prohibition of disclosure to a third party, and a clear definition of responsibility in case of problems caused by the failure of the service provider to comply with our instructions, etc.

**Opinions and Complaints**  
The Korea Herald does its best to protect the personal information of its members. If you have any suggestions concerning our policy for the protection of personal information, please send them to [heemoon@heraldm.com](mailto:heemoon@heraldm.com)

**Protection of Personal Information for Children**  
Children under 14 must obtain their parents' permission before they send their personal information to others. The Korea Herald will never share the personal information of our youngest members with anyone else, nor will we send direct mail to people under 14.

**Responsibility Concerning Problems in the Protection of Personal Information**  
The Korea Herald shall not be responsible for any problems caused by the disclosure or intrusion of personal information, other than those covered by the foregoing policy for the protection of personal information.

**Staff members in charge of the protection of personal information:**

Name: Moon Hee  
Manager of Internet News Team  

We are not engaged in the practice of automatically collecting all e-mail addresses that appear on this home page. Please note that such a practice is punishable under the Information and Telecommunication Law.
